

Dušan Rychnovský rychnovskyd@gmail.com www.dusanrychnovsky.cz (+420) 705 224 922

Dušan Rychnovský

Software engineer

About me I am a software engineer with many years of experience, mostly in Java, distributed computing and C#/Azure. My biggest strengths are analytical thinking, proficiency with software engineering tools and practices and background in computer science.

You can find me at LinkedIn. You might also be interested in my Stack Overflow and GitHub accounts and my technical blog.

Experience

Microsoft, 2017 - current

Working on Dynamics Marketing, a successful marketing automation platform, which allows to elevate customer experiences and orchestrate personalized journeys across all touchpoints.

I played a major role in implementing the lead scoring and consent management systems, and in maintaining an in-house distributed computing platform, including requirements and technical design, assuring quality, continuous integration and deployment and a 24/7 livesite rotation.

C#, Azure, Kubernetes, Azure Devops

Seznam.cz, 2015 - 2017

Working on Robot, web crawling component of Seznam's fulltext-search engine, which maintains an index of multiple bilion most interesting web pages and images from all over the Internet.

I incorporated neural networks for image-content recognition, speeded up linkanalysis based signals calculation and ported it onto a new platform, added support for videos to the system for fast crawling of fresh content (such as newssites).

Java, Hadoop, Spark, HBase, Euphoria, Akka, GIT, Maven, Linux

Casenet, 2014 - 2015

Working on TruCare, an enterprise-level care management system used by large US health maintenance organizations.

I took part in building a REST API for mobile and other external clients and in the development of a platform for extending the application with third-party correspondence systems.

Java, Spring, Hibernate, Jersey, GIT, Maven

X-Center, 2011 - 2014

Working on an ECM solution used by many large hospitals, insurance companies, etc. from around the world.

Java, OpenText technologies, SVN, Maven

Education

2011 - 2014

M.S in Software Engineering at the Faculty of Mathematics and Physics, Charles University in Prague

Master Thesis: Generating of Synthetic XML Data

2008 - 2011

B.S. in Computer Science at the Faculty of Mathematics and Physics, Charles University in Prague

ate, Akka,

ting ·Reduce, rk, Eu-

ob Sto-

ure De-

sioning

er), Enan (ba-